

**KEELAN SMYTH** 

Vengatan 33, Landskrona, 26139 (+46) 765596502

keelansmyth@hotmail.com

As a graduate from the Institute of Technology Sligo in Sport with Business. I am equipped with the ability to create, implement and evaluate programs in a commercial or community setting along with skills in management, finance and computing.

My experience as a customer service advisor providing exceptional customer service on a consistent basis has demonstrated my ability to problem solve, upsell, work independently and excellent communication skills. I have been responsible for managing customer enquiries and complaints face-toface, over the phone and email. I've worked as part of small and large international teams, planning and delivering fun and professional programs to multiple age groups and abilities which has demonstrated my leadership skills and my ability to teach and mentor.

#### SKILLS

- · Problem-solving
- · Communication
- · Microsoft Office skills
- · Time management
- · Conflict resolution
- · Network administration
- · Teamwork
- · Multitasking
- · Adaptability
- · Data analysis

## LANGUAGES

- · English native
- · Swedish Studying 3C

#### EXPERIENCE

#### Physical Education Teacher and Substitute Teacher

Nov 2023 — Present

Internationella Engelska Skolan | Landskrona

- · Effectively communicated with students, parents, and colleagues to ensure clear understanding of educational goals, expectations, and progress.
- · Successfully mentored a group of 31 students.
- · Demonstrated proficiency in utilizing educational software and learning management systems to streamline administrative tasks such as grading, attendance and communication with parents.
- · Displayed strong organizational and time management skills, effectively balancing teaching responsibilities with administrative duties to ensure smooth classroom operations.
- · Communicated complex concepts in a simplified manner, ensuring students of diverse learning abilities could learn and apply the information.

## Fitness and Entertainment host (Seasonal)

*Apr 2022* — *Oct 2023* 

TUI

- · Interacting with 40+ adults and kids, presenting games and ensuring these are monitored safely.
- · Successfully collaborated with an international team to provide innovative
- · Presenting on stage and delivering an entertainment program beyond customer expectation.
- · Hosting welcome meetings and elaborating about all the company has to offer upselling added extras.
- · Represented TUI as a proud embassador for their new fitness and childcare program · Tracking and monitoring guests attendance throughout peak and low
- season and changing classes accordingly.
- · Resolving first line complaints and ensuring they are followed up with from manager.

#### **Technical Advisor**

*Nov 2020 — Apr 2023* 

Firstsource

- · Receive and deal with all initial customer enquiries in a timely manner obiding by the rules and regulations of Ofcom.
- · Providing accurate information and advice to ensure maximum customer
- satisfaction and build strong customer relationships. · Guide all customer issues to a satisfactory conclusion or escalating calls to
- relevant department when required.
- · Managing complaints successfully to get a resolve for customers.
- · Meeting target sales rate each month.
- · Attended training to maximise potential and gain awards in contact

## **Bar Staff**

Oct 2016 — May 2021

Macon's Bar

- · Manage bar displays and ensure beverages are correctly displayed to maximize business.
- · Provide general information to new staff members on bar policies and procedures.
- · Follow health and safety precautions at all times with staff members and customers.
- · Provide a high level of customer service.
- · Maintain a fully stocked inventory and order supplies, as needed.
- · Manage all cashing up procedures in the bar at end of shift.

## EDUCATION

## **Bachelor of Business (Honours)**

*Sep 2017 — Jun 2020* 

Atlantic Technological University Sligo

Upper 2nd class Bachelor of Business (Honours) Sports with Business

## A Level

Sep 2015 — Jun 2017

St. Columbs College

- · Information and communication Technologies- B
- · Applied business- B
- · Religion- C

## **GCSE**

Sep 2010 — Jun 2015

St. Patrick's & St. Bridgid's

- · Mathematics- A
- · Religion- A
- · Learning for life and work- A
- · English Language- B
- · Science- B
- · Information and communication Technologies- B
- · Physical education- B
- · Technology- C

# CERTIFICATES & COURSES

- Full clean drivers license
- EQF Level 4 Personal trainer
- NVG level 3 Personal training • NVG level 2 fitness instructor
- Level 1 and 2 IHF Community Walking Leader
- NVQ Level 2 in Contact center operations
- Disability coach level 1 • Survive and save bronze medallion